A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Catalogued Reports, Reports 13949-17726 FA739F
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017483), 1970
- Ford Foundation Letter, July 15 (Reports 017484), 1970
- Ford Foundation Letter, September 1 (Reports 017485), 1970
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 15 (Reports 017486), 1970
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017487), 1970
- Ford Foundation Letter, January 15 (Reports 017488), 1972
- Ford Foundation Letter, March 1 (Reports 017489), 1972
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 15 (Reports 017490), 1972
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 15 (Reports 017491), 1972
- Ford Foundation Letter, July 15 (Reports 017492), 1972
- Ford Foundation Letter, September 1 (Reports 017493), 1972
- Ford Foundation Letter, November 1 (Reports 017494), 1972
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 15 (Reports 017495), 1972
- Ford Foundation Letter, March 15 (Reports 017496), 1973
- Ford Foundation Letter, May 1 (Reports 017497), 1973
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 15 (Reports 017498), 1973
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017499), 1973
- Ford Foundation Letter, September 15 (Reports 017500), 1973
- Ford Foundation Letter, November 1 (Reports 017501), 1973
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 15 (Reports 017502), 1973
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017503), 1974
- Ford Foundation Letter, March 15 (Reports 017504), 1974
- Ford Foundation Letter, May 1 (Reports 017505), 1974
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 15 (Reports 017506), 1974
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017507), 1974
- Ford Foundation Letter, September 15 (Reports 017508), 1974
- Ford Foundation Letter, November 1 (Reports 017509), 1974
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 15 (Reports 017510), 1974
- Ford Foundation Letter, Vol. 5, No. 8, December 15, 1974 (Reports 017511)
  8 p.
- Decade of experiment: The fund for the advancement of education 1951-1961, April 1961 (Reports 017512)
  A report by the Fund for the Advancement of Education, detailing its first decade of operations (1951-61). The Fund was established by the Ford Foundation and supported innovative educational programs, many of which were taken up by the Foundation.
  Fund for the Advancement of Education;FAE
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017513), 1975
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017514), 1975
- Ford Foundation Letter, May 15 (Reports 017515), 1975
- Ford Foundation Letter, July 1 (Reports 017516), 1975
- Ford Foundation Letter, September 1 (Reports 017517), 1975
- Ford Foundation Letter, November 1 (Reports 017518), 1975
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 15 (Reports 017519), 1975
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 16 (Reports 017520), 1976
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017521), 1976
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017522), 1976
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017523), 1976
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017524), 1976
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017525), 1976
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017526), 1977
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017527), 1977
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017528), 1977
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017529), 1977
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017530), 1977
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017531), 1977
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017532), 1978
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017533), 1978
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017534), 1978
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017535), 1978
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017536), 1978
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017537), 1978
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017538), 1979
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017539), 1979
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017540), 1979
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017541), 1979
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017542), 1979
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017543), 1979
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017544), 1980
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017545), 1980
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017546), 1980
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017547), 1980
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017548), 1980
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017549), 1980
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017550), 1981
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017551), 1981
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017552), 1981
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017553-001), 1981
- Ford Foundation Letter, Vol. 12, No. 5, August 1, 1981 (Reports 017553-002)
  Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations -- United States -- Administration; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations -- United States -- Finance; Ford Foundation -- Administration; United States -- Minorities -- Mathematics; United States -- Universities and colleges -- Desegregation
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017554), 1981
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017555), 1981
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017556), 1982
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017557), 1982
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017558), 1982
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017559), 1982
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017560), 1982
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017561), 1982
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017562), 1983
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017563), 1983
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017564), 1983
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017565), 1983
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017566), 1983
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017567), 1983
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017568), 1984
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017569), 1984
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017570), 1984
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017571), 1984
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017572), 1984
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017573), 1984
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017574), 1985
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017575), 1985
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017576), 1985
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017577), 1985
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017578), 1985
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017579), 1985
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017580), 1986
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017581), 1986
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017582), 1986
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017583), 1986
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017584), 1986
- Ford Foundation Letter, December 1 (Reports 017585), 1986
- Ford Foundation Letter, February 1 (Reports 017586), 1987
- Ford Foundation Letter, April 1 (Reports 017587), 1987
- Ford Foundation Letter, June 1 (Reports 017588), 1987
- Ford Foundation Letter, August 1 (Reports 017589), 1987
- Ford Foundation Letter, October 1 (Reports 017590), 1987
- Ford Foundation Letter (Reports 017591), 1988
- Ford Foundation Letter (Reports 017592), 1988
- Ford Foundation Letter (Reports 017593), 1988
- Ford Foundation Letter (Reports 017594), 1988
- Ford Foundation Letter (Reports 017595), 1989
- Ford Foundation Letter (Reports 017596), 1989
- Ford Foundation Letter (Reports 017597), 1989
- Ford Foundation Letter, Spring (Reports 017598), 1990
- Ford Foundation Letter, Summer (Reports 017599), 1990
- Ford Foundation Letter, Fall/Winter (Reports 017600), 1990
- Ford Foundation Letter, Fall (Reports 017601), 1991
- Ford Foundation Letter, Winter (Reports 017602), 1991
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring (Reports 017603), 1992
  Ford Foundation Letter;Ford Foundation Report
- Ford Foundation Report, Summer (Reports 017604), 1992
- Ford Foundation Report, Fall (Reports 017605), 1992
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017606), 1992
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring (Reports 017607), 1993
- Ford Foundation Report, Summer (Reports 017608), 1993
- Ford Foundation Report, Fall (Reports 017609), 1993
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017610), 1993
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring (Reports 017611), 1994
- Ford Foundation Report, Summer (Reports 017612), 1994
- Ford Foundation Report, Fall (Reports 017613), 1994
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017614), 1995
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring (Reports 017615), 1995
- Ford Foundation Report, Summer/Fall (Reports 017616), 1995
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017617), 1996
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring (Reports 017618), 1996
  The Ford Foundation Letter was changed to The Ford Foundation Report in the Spring 1992 issue
- Ford Foundation Report, Summer/Fall (Reports 017619), 1996
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017620), 1997
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring (Reports 017621), 1997
- Ford Foundation Report, Summer/Fall (Reports 017622), 1997
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017623), 1998
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring/Summer (Reports 017624), 1998
- Ford Foundation Report, Fall (Reports 017625), 1998
- Ford Foundation Report, Fall (Reports 017626), 1999
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring/Summer (Reports 017627), 1999
- Ford Foundation Report, Fall (Reports 017628), 1999
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017629), 2000
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring (Reports 017630), 2000
  52 p.
- Ford Foundation Report, Summer (Reports 017631), 2000
- Ford Foundation Report, Fall (Reports 017632), 2000
  64 p.
  Foundation Letter, Ford Foundation Report
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017633), 2001
  72 p.
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring (Reports 017634), 2001
  55 p.
- Ford Foundation Report, Summer (Reports 017635), 2001
- Ford Foundation Report, Fall (Reports 017636), 2001
  76 p.
- The Ford Foundation's media and arts and culture grantmaking: an historical profile, 1951-2001 (Reports 017637), 2003 (Box 885, Reel R-9324)
  Arts -- Endowments -- Evaluation; Arts -- Finance; Media -- Finance; Public broadcasting -- Finance; Cultural property -- Protection -- Finance; Endowments -- Evaluation; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations -- United States -- Finance
- Democracy, social justice and media reform: a baseline study of the emerging field of media policy (Reports 017638), 2006 (Box 885, Reel R-9324)
  Mass media policy; Broadcasting policy; Communication policy; Mass media and culture; Endowments -- Evaluation; Nonprofit organizations -- Finance; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations -- Finance
- Ford Foundation Report, Fall (Reports 017639), 2002
  70 p.
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017640), 2002
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring (Reports 017641), 2002
- Ford Foundation Report, Summer (Reports 017642), 2002
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017643), 2003
  56 p.
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring (Reports 017644), 2003
  61 p.
- Ford Foundation Report, Summer (Reports 017645), 2003
- Ford Foundation Report, Fall (Reports 017646), 2003
  49 p.
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017647), 2004
  41 p.
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring (Reports 017648), 2004
  44 p.
- Ford Foundation Report, Summer (Reports 017649), 2004
- Ford Foundation Report, Fall (Reports 017650), 2004
  45 p.
- Ford Foundation Report, Winter (Reports 017651), 2005
- Ford Foundation Report, Spring-Summer (Reports 017652), 2005
  48 p.
- Ford Reports, Number One (Reports 017653), 2007
  176 p.
  Foundation Letter, Ford Foundation Report;Ford Reports
- Exit memo (Reports 017654), 2006 (Reel R-9324)
  Peace and Social Justice/Human Rights and International Cooperation;International Affairs
- Toward a more perfect union: basic skills, poor families, and our economic future (Reports 017655), 1988
  Project on Social Welfare and the American Future
  Basic education -- United States; Government policy -- United States; Vocational education -- Socially handicapped -- Education -- United States
- An American trilemma: The persistence of racialist housing patterns in the USA (Reports 017656-001), 1980
  Ford Foundation reprint
  African Americans -- Civil rights; Discrimination in Housing -- United States; African Americans -- Housing
- The common good: Social welfare and the American future (Reports 017656-002), 1989
- Reflections on a multi-racial society (Reports 017656-003), 1983
- Peace and social justice: building a more secure and equitable world through governance civil society and human r (Reports 017656-004), undated
- Challenges and opportunities for poverty reduction (Reports 017657), 2008 (Box 885, Reel R-9324)
  Handout and PowerPoint presentation that accompanied talk given on July 24, 2008.
  Poor families -- United States; Poverty -- Social aspects -- United States; Educational change -- United States; Social action -- United States; Social problems -- United States; Economic assistance, Domestic -- United States
- The United Nations in its second half-century (Reports 017658-001), 1995
  Non-governmental organizations -- United Nations
- Nine for equality under law: Civil rights litigation: A report to the Ford Foundation (Reports 017658-002), undated
- Diary of visit to India (Reports 017659) (MI 64-9), 1964 (Box 885, Box 936, Sheet MI 64-9)
  India reports Management, manpower & industry
- Starting points for the study of appropriate metalworking technology in India (mimeo) (Reports 017660) (MI 64-10), 1964 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 64-10)
  Industries -- India; Management -- India
- Research in area development at SIET Institute (mimeo) (Reports 017661) (MI 64-12), 1964 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 64-12)
  Industries -- India; Rural development -- India; Management -- India
- Sensitivity training in regular courses - 1 (Reports 017662), 1965 (Box 886)
- Memorandum summarizing current status of Ford Foundation's management program in India's public sector enterprises and suggesting next steps (Reports 017663) (MI 65-6), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-6)
- Inter-institutional faculty development programme (mimeo) (Reports 017664) (MI 65-8), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-8)
- Leadership in a developing society (mimeo) (Reports 017665) (MI 65-9), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-9)
- Sensitivity training for personal and organisational development (Reports 017666) (MI 65-10), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-10)
- Manpower development in Nepal (mimeo) (Reports 017667) (MI 65-11), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-11)
  Industries -- Nepal; Management -- Nepal
- Developing leadership skill through sensitivity training (Reports 017668) (MI 65-12), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-12)
- Laboratory trainng in regular courses - 3 (mimeo) (Reports 017669) (MI 65-13), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-13)
- Final report on manpower and employment in India (mimeo) (Reports 017670) (MI 65-14), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-14)
  Industries -- India; Management -- India; Employment -- India
- Observations on the Ford Foundation assisted project at the Indian Institute of Management, Ahmedabad (mimeo) (Reports 017671) (MI 65-17), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-17)
- Project analysis for industrial development (mimeo) (Reports 017672) (MI 65-21), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-21)
- Sponsorship and management for industrial advisory services (mimeo) (Reports 017673) (MI 65-22), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-22)
- A special review of current developments in industrial psychology in India and two SITRA conference reports (mimeo), Spring (Reports 017674) (MI 65-23), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-23)
  Industries -- India
- Terminal report -- Small Industry Extension Training Institute, 1961-5 (mimeo) (Reports 017675) (MI 65-25), 1965 (Box 886, Box 936, Sheet MI 65-25)
- Discussion paper - Introduction of fees for selected SISI services (Reports 017676) (MI 65-26), 1965 (Box 936, Sheet MI 65-26)
- An almost consistent intertemporal model for India's fourth and fifth plans (mimeo) (Reports 017677) (MI 65-27), 1965 (Box 936, Sheet MI 65-27)
- Attributes of members in an American Union, 1966 - Indian Journal of Industrial Relations (Reports 017678) (MI 65-28) (Box 936, Sheet MI 65-28)
- Agro industries and regional growth (Reports 017679) (MI 65-29), 1965 (Box 936, Sheet MI 65-29)
  Industries -- India; Rural development -- India
- Employment policy for the fourth five year plan (mimeo) (Reports 017680) (MI 65-30), 1965 (Box 936, Sheet MI 65-30)
  Industries -- India; Employment -- India; Rural development -- India
- Management problems in Nepal (Reports 017681) (MI 66-1), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet MI 66-1)
- Observations on in-plant counselling by Small Industries Service Institute (mimeo) (Reports 017682) (MI 66-4), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet MI 66-4)
- SIET in the future or AIMS of India (mimeo) (Reports 017683) (MI 66-5), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet MI 66-5)
- Terminal Report (mimeo) (Reports 017684) (MI 66-10), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet MI 66-10)
- End of tour Report - Observations on the Ford Foundation assisted project at the Indian Institute of Management, Ahmedabad (mimeo) (Reports 017685) (MI 66-12), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet MI 66-12)
- Observations on IIM (Reports 017686) (MI 66-13), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet MI 66-13)
- Note on the concept of the administrative staff college, consultation division (mimeo) (Reports 017687) (MI 66-14), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet MI 66-14)
- The Hyerabad staff college (Reports 017688) (MI 66-15), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet MI 66-15)
- Shri Ram Centre for industrial relations - Research in progress (mimeo) (Reports 017689) (MI 66-17), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet MI 66-17)
- Labor mobility in China: a review of Ford Foundation grant making, 1997-2001 (Reports 017690-001), 2003 (Box 886, Reel R-9324)
  Labor mobility; Labor supply -- China; Manpower -- China; Labor policy -- China; Manpower policy -- China; Technical assistance -- China; Endowments -- China -- Evaluation
- Pour renover le systeme des Nations unies (Reports 017690-002), undated
- Renewing the United Nations system (Reports 017691), 1994
  09300140
  Dag Hammarskjold Foundation
  215 p.: ill.;25 cm.
  Renewing the United Nations system.
  International agencies; International cooperation
- The relevance of the technical/engineer ratio to planning (mimeo) (Reports 017692) (MI 67-1), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-1)
- Action for area development (Reports 017693), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-3)
- Outline of talk on planning on a project (mimeo) (Reports 017694) (MI 67-4), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-4)
- Policy relating to the consulting division (mimeo) (Reports 017695) (MI 67-6), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-6)
- Final report on my activities with the Joint Plant Committee (Reports 017696) (MI 67-8), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-8)
- Indian Institute of Management, Ahmedabad (mimeo) (Reports 017697) (MI 67-9), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-9)
- Status report #5, the administrative staff, College of India, Hyderbad(mimeo) (Reports 017698) (MI 67-9a), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-9a)
- Study on labour efficiency and industrial relations on ports and docks (mimeo) (Reports 017699) (MI 67-10), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-10)
  Industries -- India; Management -- India; Labor -- India
- Terminal report on assignment both at SIET and Administrative Staff College (mimeo) (Reports 017700) (MI 67-11), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-11)
- Report of the International Trade Team - Reported to the Ministry of Commerce (mimeo) (Reports 017701) (MI 67-13), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-13)
- Indian Institute of Management: Ahmedabad - A proposal for the control of public sector corporations (mimeo) (Reports 017702) (MI 67-14), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-14)
- Status report - The administrative staff College of India, Hyderbad - A.P. (consulting and applied research division) (Reports 017703) (MI 67-15), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-15)
  Industries -- India; Management--India
- Impacts of transport on labor force dynamics and manpower program actions (Reports 017704) (MI 67-21), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-21)
  Industries -- India; Management--India; Labor -- India
- Economic planning centre and state reciprocal responsibility (Reports 017705) (MI 67-22a), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-22a)
- Ahmedabad project: terminal report (mimeo) (Reports 017706) (MI 67-23), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-23)
- The role of the Foundation in the field of India (mimeo) (Reports 017707) (MI 67-26), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-26)
- Leadership in India (mimeo) (Reports 017708) (MI 67-27), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-27)
- How the Ford Foundation is related to India's manpower strategy (mimeo) (Reports 017709) (MI 67-28), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-28)
- Executive development: an analysis of management theory and its applications (Reports 017710) (MI 67-29), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet MI 67-29)
- Transcript of remarks to the Ceylon Association for the Advancement of Science, Colombo (mimeo) (Reports 017711) (MI 68-1), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet MI 68-1)
- Finances of public undertakings - a case study (mimeo) (Reports 017712) (MI 68-6), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet MI 68-6)
- Practical training or industrial experience: the joint responsibility of the university and industry (mimeo) (Reports 017713) (MI 68-7), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet MI 68-7)
- Collegialized management and its effects: quasi-experiment with administrative style in a university (mimeo) (Reports 017714) (MI 68-8), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet MI 68-8)
- Draft memorandum on Indian legal education (mimeo) (Reports 017715) (EL 60-3), 1960 (Box 936, Sheet EL 60-3)
  Overseas Division/South and Southeast Asia;International Division/South and Southeast Asia/International Division/Asia and the Pacific
  India Reports;Education-Law
  Law schools -- India; Law -- Study and teaching -- India
- Draft report of the Gajendragadkar Committee (mimeo) (Reports 017716) (EL 64-1), 1964 (Box 936, Sheet EL 64-1)
- Discussion paper: proposals respecting the Delhi Law Faculty (mimeo) (Reports 017717) (EL 66-1), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EL 66-1)
- Report on short-term assignment (mimeo) (Reports 017718) (EL 66-2), 1966 (Box 936, Sheet EL 66-2)
- Progress report on grant to Law College, Banaras Hindu University (mimeo), July 1966 to (Reports 017719) (EL 67-1), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EL 67-1)
- Proposal for discussing relations between the Indian Law Institute and the Law Faculties of Banaras Hindu and Delhi Universities (mimeo) (Reports 017720) (EL 67-2), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EL 67-2)
- Cooperation on problems of legal education and legal research in India (mimeo) (Reports 017721) (EL 67-3), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EL 67-3)
- Status of the grant to Banaras Hindu University Law College (mimeo) (Reports 017722) (EL 67-4), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EL 67-4)
- Confidential terminal report (mimeo) (Reports 017723) (EL 67-5), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EL 67-5)
- Development planning and the power of acquisition of property (mimeo) (Reports 017724) (EL 67-7), 1967 (Box 936, Sheet EL 67-7)
- A training program for Indian law teachers - some perspectives (mimeo) (Reports 017725) (EL 68-1), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet EL 68-1)
- Observations and impressions of Delhi University Faculty of Law (mimeo) (Reports 017726) (EL 68-3), 1968 (Box 936, Sheet EL 68-3)